Adam Juwig

1314 W. University Dr. Apt 40 Tempe, AZ (480) 717-1005 ADAMJUWIG@GMAIL.COM

Restaurant manager with 10+ years experience of managing front of house and back of house operations in multiple fast paced and high volume restaurants. Skilled at training and overseeing staff to provide outstanding customer service while ensuring high food quality and safety standards. Currently pursuing a career in web and software development.

Experience

Hillside Spot Cafe & Market - Phoenix, AZ

January 2012 - Present

Assistant General Manager - June 2014 - Present

- Training and employee development
- Recruiting and hiring
- Purchase and maintain inventory with attention to budget guidelines
- Monitor kitchen operations for consistent food quality, sanitation, and presentation
- Assist in creating menu and beverage specials
- Oversee scheduling of 30+ personnel
- Control labor costs
- Problem solving under high pressure while maintaining a positive attitude
- Maintain relations with staff and customers, reducing turnover
- Administrate Aloha and Square Point of Sale Systems

Barista & Bar Supervisor - May 2012 - Present

- Create seasonal coffee and alcohol specials
- Train staff on proper and safe service of alcoholic beverages

- Maintenance of espresso machines for high performance and functionality
- Oversee orders of all craft beer, wine, and coffee

Education

University of Arizona - Full Stack Coding Bootcamp - In Progress

Mesa Community College - Mesa, AZ - August 2008 - May 2012

Mountain Pointe High School - Phoenix, AZ - August 2003 - May 2007

Additional Skills

- Knowledgeable in HTML, Javascript, and CSS languages
- Experienced with social media marketing and online branding
- Small business management
- Volunteer at The Welcome to America Project
- Successful musician with 50,000,000+ streams, 300,000+ albums sold, live touring and performances worldwide in 6+ countries